perfumersapprentice.com 2019-04-14

# Privacy Policy

**Effective Date: 10/23/2014 **

_**This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.perfumersapprentice.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:**_

**Information Collected:**

  * We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

  * 

**Sharing:  
**  
The information we collect is used solely for order fulfillment and customer contact in the rare occurence we need to reach our customers for technical issues regarding an order or inquiry. 

  * You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided on our website:

    * See what data we have about you, if any.
    * Change/correct any data we have about you.
    * Have us delete any data we have about you.
    * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
    *     * 

**Correcting Information:**

  * Our customers have full control over changing their own information by logging into their account, and going to account settings and altering applicable fields therein. All customers must have an account to have information stored in our system, which is an added security setting preventing hackers and competitors from obtaining unwanted personal information.
  *   

**Site Security:**

  * Customer information Security, Click [Here](http://shop.perfumersapprentice.com/t-security.aspx). 

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

  * While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

  *   * **Policy Changes:**  

  * If Customer Information policy changes occur, it will be communicated on this webpage first, and any customers who have chosen to allow us to send emails to them will also receive notification regarding privacy policy changes as well. 
  *   

**Concerns:**

  * Any concerns regarding misuse of personal information should be directed directly to the owner via phone or email (Admin@PerfumersApprentice.com).

***********************  
**  
**

**Registration**  

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the products/services on our site in which you have expressed interest. At your option, you may also provide demographic information (such as gender or age) about yourself, but it is not required.  
**  
****  
Orders** 

We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

**Links**  

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

*****************************

The Perfumer’s Apprentice is fully committed to maintaining customer privacy and will therefore only use your information to fulfill orders and inform you of special events and promotions. Your information will not be sold/given or used in any other way without your permission. Our sole purpose is to provide our customers with what they need, without any of the hassle or worries that come along with sharing information. When you shop with us you can have complete confidence that your information will not be shared, because after all we are people just like you.

~ Linda Andrews (Owner)
